aussiebum.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy on aussieBum online store

Effective starting: March 26, 2014

Introduction 

This Privacy Policy explains what information aussieBum collects about you and why, what we do with that information, how we share it, and how we handle the content you place in our online and offline systems. By providing your Personal Information, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy. 

##  Scope of Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy applies to the information that we obtain through your interaction with the aussieBum website and services via a "Device" or when you otherwise interact with aussieBum. 

“aussieBum services” include, but not limited to our: 

  * Websites 
  * Customer Service Systems 
  * Customer Order Processing Systems 

A **"Device"** is any computer used to access the aussieBum Services, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other electronic device. 

Unless otherwise stated, our websites, Customer Service Systems and Customer Order Processing Systems are treated the same for the purposes of this document. By registering for or using aussieBum Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. 

##  Information you provide to us 

We collect the following information: 

Content: 
     We collect and store Content that you create, input, submit, post, upload, transmit, store or display in the process of using our Websites. Such Content includes any Personal Information or other sensitive information that you choose to include. 
Account and Profile Information: 
     We collect information about you and your company as you register for an aussieBum account, create or modify your profile, make purchases through, use, access, or interact with aussieBum Services (including but not limited to when you upload, download, collaborate on or share Content). Information we collect includes but is not limited to your name, username, address, email address, phone number, profile photo, job title, or credit card details. You may provide this information directly when you enter it in aussieBum Services. If you are providing information (including Personal Information) about someone else, such as buying a gift to be directly shipped to the other person, you confirm that you have the authority to act for them and they consent to the collection and use of their Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 
Other submissions: 
     We collect other data that you submit to our Websites or as you participate in any interactive features of the aussieBum Services, participate in a survey, contest, promotion, sweepstakes, activity or event, apply for a job, request customer support, communicate with us via third party social media sites or otherwise communicate with us. For example, information regarding a problem you are experiencing with an aussieBum product could be submitted to our Customer Service Department or posted in our public forums. Any information, including Personal Information that you submit to our Websites could be visible to the public unless submitted to a secure area in the Website. 

##  Information we collect from your use of aussieBum Services 

Web Logs: 
     As is true with most websites and services delivered over the Internet, we gather certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our Websites and Services. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses as well as browser type, internet service provider, URLs of referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, information you search for, locale and language preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, and system configuration information. Occasionally, we connect Personal Information to information gathered in our log files as necessary to improve aussieBum Services for individual customers. 
Analytics Information from Website: 
     We and our analytics provider collect and store analytics information when you use our Websites and Services to help us improve our products and services.  
The analytics information we collect includes elements of Content related to the function the user is performing. As such, the analytics information we collect may include Personal Information or sensitive business information that the user has included in Content that the user chose to upload, submit, post, create, transmit, store or display in an aussieBum Service. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Google Analytics as an analytics provider. To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, refer to Google's Policies and Principles. Use the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on to prevent to analytics information from being sent to Google Analytics. 
Analytics Information Derived from Content: 
     Analytics information also consists of data we collect as a result of running queries against Content across our user base for the purposes of generating Usage Data. "Usage Data" is aggregated data about a group or category of services, features or users that does not contain Personal Information. For example, we may query Content to determine the most common types of products and promotional assets that users are most interested in.  
Though we may happen upon sensitive or Personal Information as we compile Usage Data from Content across user instances, this is a byproduct of our efforts to understand broader patterns and trends. It is not a concerted effort by us to examine the Content of any particular customer. 
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: 
     We use various technologies to collect information, including cookies that we save to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory. We use cookies to improve and customize aussieBum Services and your experience; to allow you to access and use the Websites without re-entering your username or password; and to count visits and understand which areas and features of the Websites and Services are most popular. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of our Websites or Services. We also collect information using web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels"). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Websites or in emails that help us to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. 

##  Information we collect from other sources 

Information from third party services: 
     We also obtain information from third parties and combine that with information we collect through aussieBum Services. For example, we may have access to certain information from a third party social media or authentication service if you log into aussieBum Services through the service or otherwise provide us with access to information from the service. Any access that we may have to such information from a third party social or authentication service is in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by that service. By authorizing us to connect with a third party service, you authorize us to access and store your name, email address(es), current city, profile picture URL, and other information that the third party service makes available to us, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You should check your privacy settings on these third party services to understand and change the information sent to us through these services. 

##  How we use Information we collect 

When you shop with aussieBum the personal information we use may include your: 

  * Name 
  * Delivery Address 
  * Email Address 
  * Telephone Number 
  * Mobile Number 
  * Date of Birth 

The personal information we collect from you will be used in some or all of the following ways: 

  * To deliver the products you have purchased from aussieBum. I.e. couriers and local postal delivery services (who we arrange to deliver goods to you on our behalf) 
  * To update you on the delivery of the product and for customer support purposes 
  * To provide you with relevant product information 
  * To customize future shopping for you and improve our store. 

General Uses. We use the information we collect about you for a variety of purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, operate, maintain, improve, and promote aussieBum Services; 
  * Enable you to access and use aussieBum Services, including uploading, downloading, collaborating on and sharing Content; 
  * Process and complete transactions, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices; 
  * Communicate with you, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests; providing customer service and support; providing you with information about services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests and events; providing other news or information about us and our select partners; and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages. Generally, you have the ability to opt out of receiving any promotional communications as described below under “Your Choices”; 
  * Process and deliver contest or sweepstakes entries and rewards; 
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with aussieBum Services and for marketing or advertising purposes; 
  * Investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to aussieBum Services, and other illegal activities; 
  * Personalize aussieBum Services, including by providing content, features, or advertisements that match your interests, language and preferences; 
  * Enable you to communicate, collaborate, and share Content with users you designate; and 
  * For other purposes about which we notify you. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not use Personal Information appearing in our Analytics Logs or Web Logs for any purpose. 

##  Information sharing and disclosure 

We will not share or disclose any of your Personal Information or Content with third parties except as described in this policy. We do not sell your Personal Information or Content. 

Your use: 
     When you use aussieBum Services, Content you provide will be displayed back to you. Certain features of aussieBum Services allow you to make some of your Content public, in which case it will become readily accessible to anyone. We urge you to consider the sensitivity of any data you make public. 
Access by aussieBum Customer Services and the aussieBum IT system administrators: 
     You should be aware that the administrator of your instance of aussieBum Services may be able to: 

  * access information in and about your aussieBum Services account; 
  * disclose, restrict, or access information that you have provided or that is made available to you when using your aussieBum Services account, including your Content; and 
  * Control how your aussieBum Services account may be accessed or deleted. 

aussieBum Community: 
     Our Websites offer publicly accessible community services such as blogs and customer comments. You should be aware that any Content you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Your posts may remain even after you cancel your account. Service Providers, Business Partners and Others: We work with third party service providers to provide website, application development, hosting, maintenance, back-up, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, analysis and other services for us. These third parties may have access to or process your Information as part of providing those services for us. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Our Rights: We may disclose your Information (including your Personal Information) to a third party if (a) we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (b) to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) to protect the security or integrity of aussieBum's products and services, (d) to protect aussieBum, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) to respond to an emergency which we believe in the good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person. 
Business Transfers: 
     We may share or transfer your information (including your Personal Information) in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. 
Aggregated or Anonymized Data: 
     We may also share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you with the third parties described above. 
With Your Consent: 
     We will share your personal information with third parties when we have your consent to do so. 

##  Information we do not share 

We do not share Personal Information about you with third parties for their marketing purposes (including direct marketing purposes) without your permission. 

##  Data storage, transfer and security 

aussieBum hosts data with hosting service providers in numerous countries including the United States and Australia. The servers on which Personal Information is stored are kept in a controlled environment. While we take reasonable efforts to guard your Personal Information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. In addition, we cannot guarantee that any passively-collected Personal Information you choose to store in Websites or Services are maintained at levels of protection to meet specific needs or obligations you may have relating to that information. 

Where data is transferred over the Internet as part of a Website or Service, the data is encrypted using industry standard SSL (HTTPS). 

##  Your Choices 

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from aussieBum by using the unsubscribe link within each email, updating your email preferences at www.ausiebum.com, or emailing us to have your contact information removed from our promotional email list or registration database. Although opt-out requests are usually processed immediately, please allow ten (10) business days for a removal request to be processed. Even after you opt out from receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive transactional messages from us regarding aussieBum’s Services. 

##  Accessing and updating your information 

You can access and amend some of the information we keep about you through your account settings. 

Contacting This Website: 
     If you have any questions about this Statement, the practices of aussieBum with respect to personal information or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at help@aussiebum.com 

##  Access to Your Personal Information and Complaints Procedure 

1.1 Under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), you have certain rights to access the personal information we collect and hold about you.  
1.2 Generally, subject to the exceptions of APP 12.3, we will allow an individual access to the personal information we hold about them within a reasonable time after it is requested. When requesting such access please identify the precise type/s of information requested.?You may make a request by contacting our Customer Service Team at help@aussiebum.com  
1.3 We take those steps reasonable in the circumstances to ensure that the personal information that we collect, use and disclose is accurate, up to date and complete. Where an individual requests to correct information, we will take reasonable steps to correct the information, having regard to the purpose for which it is held. You may lodge a request to correct personal information in the manner outlined in clause 1.2 above.  
1.4 To make a complaint about a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles, which includes how we handle your personal information, you may contact our Customer Service Team. We will endeavor to respond to your complaint within a reasonable time after it is received. If you are not satisfied by our response, you may acquire further information regarding privacy from the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner. 

##  Compliance with privacy laws and regulations 

You agree not to use the aussieBum Services in a manner that would violate laws protecting an individual’s privacy rights, health or financial data, including the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 as amended (HIPAA) and the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act and its implementing regulations, the Privacy Rule and the Safeguards Rule. 

##  Our policy towards children 

aussieBum Services are not directed to individuals under 13. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact our Support Services. 

##  International users 

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your Personal Information to Australia and the United States to us. By providing your Personal Information, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy. 

##  Definitions 

aussieBum Services: 
     aussieBum’s Websites, Customer Service Systems and Customer Order Processing Systems. 
Content: 
     any information or data that you upload, submit, post, create, transmit, store or display in an aussieBum Service. 
Downloadable Products and Content: 
     aussieBum’s downloadable content and mobile applications, including Add-ons created by aussieBum, that are installed by customers on an infrastructure of their choice. Downloadable Products do not include Add-Ons created by third parties, even when they are accessed through aussieBum.com. 
Information: 
     all of the different forms of data, content, and information collected by us as described in this Privacy Policy. 
Personal Information: 
     information that may be used to readily identify or contact you as an individual person, such as| name, address, email address, or phone number. Personal Information does not include information that has been anonymised such that it does not allow for the ready identification of specific individuals. 
Websites: 
     aussieBum's websites, including but not limited to aussiebum.com, aussiebum.com.au and any related websites, sub-domains and pages. 

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, where appropriate we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the login screen or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use aussieBum Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. 

If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy, you will need to stop using aussieBum Services and deactivate your account(s).
